（諫冬）おかしいな。
出掛けちゃってるのかな？
That's strange... I wonder if they went out?
（邦枝）この祠を管理してる人？→
Tengu Daimei Shrine
The person who's in charge of this shrine?
そもそもここって何が祀られて…。
And wait... What's enshrined here anyway?
（諫冬）戻ってきたみたい。
（邦枝）何が？
Looks like they're back.
Who?
はっ！うっ…。
（コマちゃんの声）
諫冬以外の人間の立入りを
許したおぼえはないで。誰や　お前。
I do not recall allowing any human
other than Isafuyu to enter here.
Who are you?
この人は　邦枝　葵さんと言います。話を聞いて下さい。→
Her name is Kunieda Aoi-san!
Please listen to what we have to say!
悪魔と戦う方法が
知りたくて来たんです。
Tengu Daimei Shrine
She came here to learn how to fight Demons!
あ…。
（ギャアギャア）
（レイミア）
あなたがたの勝手な行動に対する
処分（しょぶん）が下されました。
The punishment for your insubordinate
actions has been decided upon.
（グラフェル）勝手な行動？心外だな。→
Insubordination? That's unexpected.
オレたちは　焔王様のために
動いただけだ。→
Everything we did was for Lord En.
くだらん功名心など
一握りも　ありはしない。
We weren't thinking of claiming the glory
of victory for ourselves whatsoever.
（レイミア）それについては疑いません。
I have no doubts about that.
何より失敗してきたというのが
問題なのです。
The fundamental problem is
the fact that you failed.
（ヘカドス）契約者自体は
たいしたことなかった。→
The contract holder himself
was nothing special.
あの男さえ来なければ…。
If that man hadn't shown up...
そこで…。
About that...
（ナーガ）待たせたな。
（グラフェル）ナーガ。
Sorry I took so long.
Naga...
（ヘカドス）うっ…転送玉。
The Transfer Jewel!
（レイミア）ベヘモット団長の言葉を
そのまま伝えます。
I will now tell you exactly
what Captain Behemoth said:
「負けて　おめおめ
帰ってくんじゃねぇ！→
"If yer gonna lose, don't come slinkin' back!
やるんなら最後までやれ！！」
だそうです。
If yer gonna do it, then
follow through to the end!"
...is what he said.
ありがてぇ。さすが団長。
Thank you... I'd expect nothing
less from the Captain.
すぐに兵隊を集めろ。雪辱戦だ。
Gather the troops! We'll
soon have our revenge!
Sorry to Have Kept You Waiting
（ラミア）へっくしゅっ！
（古市）風邪か？
A cold?
（神崎）無理もねえ。もう丸３日も
徹夜でゲームやってんだ。→
Wouldn't surprise me...
We've been playing games
through the night three days in a row...
ガキには　キツイだろ…。
Must be hard for the kiddies.
（古市）てゆ～か
なんでこんなことに…。→
But... how did this happen?
オレたち勝ちましたよね…。
We won, didn't we?
（夏目）勝ったよ。でも　そのあと
向こうが　ゴネたじゃん。
We did. And then they were all like:
（焔王）((今のはナシじゃ～っ！→
That didn't count!
今度は　別のゲームで勝負じゃ～！
１００回　勝負じゃ～っ！！))
Let's play a different game this time!
Best outta a hundred!
（ラミア）いっつもこうなのよ。
忘れてたわ。
He's always like this... I'd forgotten.
あいつゲームで　負けを
認めたことなんてないんだから。→
There's no way he'll accept
that he lost at a game.
こっちが負けてあげるまで　永遠に
もう１回って言い続けるわよ。
Until we lose, he'll keeping going
"One more time!" for eternity.
（神崎）おいおい　じゃあ今までの
勝負はなんだったんだ？
Whoa there... So, what was
the point of this again?
もうやめだ　やめ！
I quit. I'm out.
So, you two have played
games together before?
つ～か　一緒にゲームしたりなんか
してたんだな　焔王と。
昔　嫌というほどね。
Back then, till I was sick of it.
ん！？そんなに仲がいいなら→
If you're so close with him, why
don't you call him yourself?
ラミアから呼び掛けてみたら
いいんじゃね？
これ　ネトゲなんだし！
は？
It's an online game, after all.
いや…あの…
それはちょっと困るというか。
Uh... That's... It might
be a little problem...
"It's been so long, Lord Enny-wenny!"
"It's Lamia, tee-hee!"
（古市）送信っと。
Send...
てゆ～か　何そのメール！
私　バカ！？
And wait, what the hell is that message?!
Do you think I'm an idiot?!
（神崎）
ちょっとパンチ足りなくね？
Don't you think it requires a bit more oomph?
（古市）もう少し
リアリティ足してみます？
You mean, something more... real?
（夏目）
ハートマーク　いっぱいつける
女とか　オレ嫌いなんだよね～。
I totally hate girls who put lots
of heart marks in their messages.
自分で打つ！自分で打つから～！！
[外:CA272052D9AD97FC1910C3006785F102]（メールの受信音）
I'll type it myself! I'll
type it myself, damn it!
（神崎）おっ！もう返信が来たぞ。
あっ。
He's already responded.
なになに？
「ぬぉぉぉぉぉっっ！！→
Let's see here...
"Oooh, Lamia! Lamia, is
it? Why are you here?"
ラミアー！！ラミアかっっ！！
なぜ　お主がっっっ！…」。
"Where are you? Are you coming here now?"
めっちゃ食い付いた。
Hook, line, and sinker.
（神崎）
やっぱ　この路線だな。
「イヤーン　ウフーン　バカーン。→
Yup, this is our ticket!
"Oh, my! Tee-hee, likes, whoa! I'm
so there! There like a square!
きてるきてる～えれきてる～。→
ず～っと　あなたのことを
探してるのよ～。→
I've been searching for you likes, forever!
レッツ　ＴＯ　ＬＯＶＥる　ダークネス！」。
送信っと。
Let's To Love-Ru Darkness!"
And, send.
（ラミア）もうやめてぇ～っ！
[外:CA272052D9AD97FC1910C3006785F102]（メールの受信音）
Please, stop!
（神崎）
返信　はえ～。
こいつ絶対　お前のこと好きだぞ。
That was fast.
He totally has a thing for you.
（寧々）「余はいつでもお前のことを
大切に思っているぞ？」。
"You've always held a
special place in my heart."
（由加）うわ～っ！なにこれ
なにこれ！？カレシっすか？
What's this?! What's this?!
He's your boyfriend?
こっちも食いついた。
Looks like this one's hooked, too.
神崎先輩っ！
オレにも貸してくださいっ！
Kanzaki-senpai, let me! Let me!
古市…ちょっ　もう！
ホントにやめなさいよ！
Furuichi... Hey...
Stop it, for real!
（古市）大丈夫　大丈夫っ！
Don't you worry.
「古市です。ラミアがとても坊っちゃま
に会いたがってますよ！！」。
"This is Furuichi. Lamia really
wants to meet you, Lord En.
We'll take her to you, so please
tell us where you're at?"
[外:CA272052D9AD97FC1910C3006785F102]（メールの送信音）
フワァ～。
（一同）う～ん。
（古市）また返信が
ピタリと止まった…。
And... suddenly there's no response again.
（コンビニ店員）
ありがとうございました～。
Please come again!
（夏目）せっかく
チャンスだったのにね～。（古市）すみません。
And I'd thought this was our big chance...
I'm sorry...
（ラミア）いいのよ。あたし
アイツ　苦手だから。→
It's okay. I can't really handle him.
正直　会わずにホッとしてるし。
Honestly I'm relieved that
I don't have to see him.
まあ　確かにあんな一方的な
感じだと　ちょっとね～。
It's true that being so
one-sided is a little...
いやいや　ラミたんも
すみに　おけね～ッスな。
But man, Lami-tan, you're a smooth operator.
（ラミア）ラミたん？
にしても　ど～っすかな。
Lami-tan?
Anyway, what'll we do?
もうマジで
打つ手ナシじゃ…。お？
We're seriously outta options.
（ヨルダ）あっ…。
（由加）お　いつぞやのキャリアウーマン。
（ラミア）ヨルダ…。
It's that career woman...
Yolda!
ちょ…待って！
Wha... Wait!
ん？ん？
（ヨルダ）ハァハァ…。
（古市・ラミア）ハァハァ…。
（ヨルダ）早く早く早く…！
うわっ　ははっ　ハァハァ…。
Hurry! Hurry and open!
（古市・ラミア）ハァハァ…。
ハァハァ…。
ウエ～。
ハァハァハァ…。
あっ　えっ　ここは？
This is...
オレたちのいたフロア！？
The floor we've been on?!
（焔王）ヨルダ～　余のポテチは
まだかのぅ～。
Yolda, do you have those
potato chips I wanted?
坊っちゃま！
出てこないで下さいっ！
Master, please don't come outside!
い　い　い　いたぁ～っ！
っていうか　となり～！？
There he is!
And...
He was next door!
ん？
なに騒いでるのよ　古市っ！
What's all the ruckus about, Furuichi?!
あ…おう？
Sorry about this... We've finally
found a game partner for Lord En,
ごめんなさいね。せっかくできた→
焔王坊っちゃまの
ゲーム相手ですもの。
このまま続けてもらうわ。
so you won't be stopping any time soon.
（古市）
《ずっと隣の部屋にいたのかよ。→
He's been in the room next
door the entire time?
住み着いて１週間ってとこか。→
Living in here for an entire week?
まあ確かに考えてみりゃ
こんな理想的な場所もね～わな。→
Well, thinking about it,
there'd be no better place.
広いし　ゲーム設備は完璧だし
ってゆ～か　部屋汚ね～。→
There's plenty of room, and it has
every game system you could want.
And man, this room's a mess!
侍女悪魔３人もいて
何してんだよ…》
What the hell are his three
Demon Maidservants doing?!
（イザベラ）あなたは確か
ベルゼ様の契約者→
You're the slave of Beelze-sama's
contract holder,
男鹿とかいう人間の
奴隷でしたわね。
That human named Oga, yes?
いや　奴隷って…。
Um, I wouldn't say slave...
名前は確か…。
（サテュラ）ふるちん！
Your name is...
Furuchin!
あれ？違うっけか？
Wait, that's not it?
すみません　今なんて？
ふるちん！
Excuse me... What was that again?
Furuchin!
え？もう１回。
Um, say that once again.
（サテュラ）ふるちん？
もう１回！もっと感情を込めて！！
Furuchin?
Once more! And put more feeling into it!
やめなさいっ！
ラミア　あなたも久しぶりですね。
Stop this.
Lamia... It's been quite a while.
（サテュラ）
にしても　ちょっと
見つかんの　はえ～よな～。→
But man, sure found us quick.
だから　もっとちゃんと
変装しろっつったんだよ　ヨルダ。
I told you to disguise yourself
more carefully, Yolda!
（ヨルダ）
変装して行ったじゃない。
ヒゲ眼鏡じゃ余計に目立つでしょ。
I did! The mustache glasses just
make me stand out more, you know?
（サテュラ）
つ～か　向こうで着替えろよ！
And change over there!
（ヨルダ）あらぁ～ごめんなさいね。→
Oh, sorry about that.
そっちの男の子には
ちょっと刺激が強すぎたかしら。
I suppose this might come to too much
of a shock to that boy over there.
いえっ　まったく気にせず
どうぞ続けてください！
No, I do not mind in the
slightest! Please, proceed!
《ていうか　何このぬるい空気。
私たちに見つかったのに→
Wait, what's with this "whatever" attitude?
We've found them, but they
don't seem upset in the least!
まったく慌てるそぶりがない。
どういうつもり？》
What are they planning?
（古市）え～と…ところで
焔王坊っちゃんは？
By the way, where is Lord En?
さっきまで　そこにいましたよね？
He was just here before, right?
坊っちゃまは　ああ見えて
シャイですから。
The Master might not seem
like it, but he is quite shy.
ラ　ラミア…。
La-Lamia?
（古市）
《もじもじ　してらっしゃる》
（焔王）ラーミア。
He's all fidgety!
Lamia!
《焔王　面倒くせぇ～！》
Lord En is such a pain!
古市　やっぱりここは
いったん引上げましょ。
Furuichi, I think we should
get out of here for now.
私たちだけで
交渉を進めるのは危険だわ。
It's dangerous for us to continue
these negotiations on our own!
こら～っ　人間！余の嫁に
馴れ馴れしく　近づくなっ！
Hey you, Human!
Don't get so friendly there with my wife!
燃やすぞっ！
誰が嫁よ！→
I'll burn you to a crisp!
Your wife my butt!
アンタは馴れ馴れしい通り越して
ず～ず～しいのよ！このバーカ！
You're an annoying, prissy worrywart!
You big dummy!
アッハハ　いいのかよ
王族にそんな口きいて…。はっ！
Are you sure you should be
speaking to royalty like that?
あ？
ん！！
《よくねぇ～っ！
これ全然　よくねぇぞぉ～！！》
Not good!
This is not good at all!
ラミア　帰ろう！確かにお前の
言う通りだ。いったん戻…。
Lamia, let's go. You were totally right.
Let's go back, and...
（ヨルダ）まあまあ　そう言わず。→
Now now, don't be like that.
せっかく来たんだから
ゲームでもしていきなさいよ。
Now that you're here and all...
Let's play a game or something...
（焔王）
うむ。そうじゃの　人間。
かくなる上は　それしかなかろう。
Yes. That's right, Human.
That's the only thing left to do...
ラミアを賭けて
余とゲーム勝負じゃっ！
You and I will do battle
with games for Lamia's hand!
えええ～っ！？
だから　なんで私を賭けるのよ！
バカ！？あんたバカなの？
Why are you betting me?!
Are you an idiot?! Are you a total idiot?!
（イザベラ・サテュラ・ヨルダ）はぁ！！
（パキン！）
ひゃっはぁ～っ！
（邦枝）はあっ！たあっ！→
いやああっ！
心月流抜刀術　弐式…。
Shingetsuryuu Sword School, Second Style...
Demon Clad...
Countless Petals Scattering Sakura Blossoms!
すごい　葵ちゃん…。
Wow, Aoi-chan...
（夏目）
あれ？古市君とラミアちゃん
帰ってないの？
Oh? Didn't Furuichi-kun
and Lamia-chan come back?
I thought they were with you.
（神崎）一緒じゃなかったのかよ。
Um, we were together for a bit, but...
いや～途中まで
一緒だったんだけど…。
They went chasing after this career woman.
なんか　キャリアウーマンの
おね～さん追っ掛けていって。
（姫川）≪お前ら≫
（夏目）姫ちゃん。
You guys...
Hime-chan?
（姫川）対戦相手の居場所
つきとめたぞ。
I've figured out where the
person we've been playing is.
（神崎）マジかよ？
（姫川）フッ…なんてことはねぇ。
Seriously?
It wasn't much...
Once I researched the terminal they were
using to connect to the net, I got a hit.
ネット上で相手先の端末調べりゃ
一発だったんだよ。→
それより　どこだと思うよ？
ちょっと笑えるぞ？
So, where do you think it was?
You're gonna have a laugh at this.
（ベル坊）アヒャヒャ…。
You're shittin' me.
（神崎）マジかよ！？…つか
隣も　お前の部屋だろ！
And wait... This is your room too, isn't it?
Hiding in the shadow of
the lighthouse, is it?
（夏目）灯台下暗しってやつか…。
Wouldn't you normally realize this?
（神崎）気づかね～か　ふつ～。
（姫川）我ながらマヌケな話だぜ。
Honestly, it's my fault here.
I underestimated him.
ナメやがって。悪魔野学園だか
なんだか知らんが→
I don't know what this Akumano Academy is
or whatever... But it's time to finish this!
きっちり　カタつけてやる。
Wait, Furuichi! What are you trying to...
エッ…エッ…。
（ラミア）ちょっと古市　どうする気！？
下ろしなさいよっ！
Let me down!
Shut it! We've gotta run!
うるせぇ！こうなったら
逃げるしかないだろ！
Hey! That's far enough!
オラ～っ！！…そこまでだ！
（姫川）えっ…あれ？
Huh?
（古市）なっ…！？
It's no use.
（ヨルダ）無駄よ。今　この部屋は→
This room is now in a separate
dimension, cut off from the outside.
外界から切り離した
別次元にあるの。→
逃げられないし
助けも来ないわ。
You can't escape, nor will help reach you.
It's true. Yolda is the same as Alaindelon.
本当よ。ヨルダはアランドロンと
同じ次元転送悪魔なの。
She's a Dimensional Transfer Demon.
Oh, please don't put me in the
same boat as that old man.
あら　あんな　おっさんと
一緒にしないでもらえます？
明らかにレベルが違うでしょう。
I mean, I'm clearly on
a whole different level.
No...
（古市）そんな…。
いちかばちか飛び降りてみる？
Let's go for broke and jump in.
運が良ければ　どこかに
繋がってるかもしれないわ。
If luck's with us, it'll
connect to somewhere.
I really wouldn't recommend that.
やめておいた方がいいわよ　それ→
私も責任もてないから
…っていうか→
I won't take responsibility
for what happens to you...
And besides, it's not like we're
trying to kill you or anything...
別に命を狙ってるわけでも
ないんだし…→
Let's have fun playing games together...
楽しくゲーム…しましょうよ。
（通信機：ヒルダの声）
生憎だな　ヨルダ。→
Sorry to break the news, Yolda.
But you should not underestimate Alaindelon.
アランドロンを
みくびらん方がいいぞ。
This is Miss Hilda's communication device!
（ラミア）
これ　ヒルダ姉さまの通信機。
いつの間に！？
When did it...
（通信機：ヒルダの声）
今回のことを　お前に頼んだ以上→
Besides the favor I asked you, it's only
natural to have a little insurance, yes?
これくらいの保険は当然だろう。
（ラミア）ヒルダ姉さま…。
Miss Hilda?
（通信機：ヒルダの声）
２人とも　下がっていろ。
Stand back, you two.
Impossible...
まさか…通信機から
肉体を転送…そんなことが？
Transferring a living body
through a communication device?!
That's...
（ヒルダ）ふむ。はじめてにしては
上出来だ。→
Yes. Quite well done for the first time.
またせたな…ラミア。
（ラミア）ヒルダ姉さま！
Sorry to keep you waiting, Lamia.
Miss Hilda!
あっ…ヒルダさ～～ん！→
Hilda-san!
I was so scared! So very scared!
怖かったよ～　怖かったよ～。
お体は大丈夫なんですか？
Are you feeling better now?
（バキッ！）
…うむ。
Yes, no need to worry.
心配するな。この通り絶好調だ。
As you can tell, I am at full health.
G-Good thing...
（古市）よ…よかったっす…。
ヒルダ　あなた一体どうやって…。
Hilda! How in the world...
フッ…。決まっているだろう。
→
アランドロンの力を借りたのだ。
Isn't it obvious?
I used Alaindelon's power.
He trained a little bit himself.
やつにも少し
修業をしてきてもらった。→
そして　会得した
新・転送術　バリサン。
And he managed to discover
a new transfer technique.
Barisan!
（アランドロン）ふう…。何とか
うまくいきましたな。→
Scattering Burrs
It went well, somehow...
My underwear shredded, though.
パンツ破けたけど…。
次元を超越する
魔界の電波を使い→
It's a bold new technique that uses
extra-dimensional Demon Electromagnetic Waves,
allowing dimensional transfer
through communication devices.
通信機から
転送を行うという荒技だ。
なによそれ。結局　自分が
一番優秀だとでも言いたいわけ？
What? So you're trying to
tell me that you're superior?
昔から　あんたのそういう所が
大嫌いだったのよ…っていうか→
That's what I've always,
always hated about you.
And besides, the thing I hate the most...
キャラかぶってんのが…
一番気に入らないのよっ！
...is how you copy my character!
たしかにな…
それは　私も同感だ。→
It's true.
I fully agree.
Maybe you'll get a bit more serious now.
これで少しは
マシになったろう。
うっ…。
次は　その髪を五分刈りに
してやろうか？
Next time, how about I chop
off all of that hair for you?
うおぉぉ～～っ
すげぇぜ　ヒルダさ～ん！
Awesome, Hilda-san!
（古市）あっ！
い…いや～もちろん
ヨルダさんも素敵ですよ～！
Well, you're pretty excellent
yourself, Yolda-san!
And I prefer you with your hair down!
…っていうか
髪おろした方が好きだな　僕→
Yo, sexy little Demon!
よっ！セクシー小悪魔！
なに言ってんのコイツ。
What's his problem?
まあ　いいわ…
そもそも　こんな狭い廊下じゃ→
Fine, enough.
It's true my weapon is at a disadvantage
here in this narrow hallway.
長い私の武器は不利だものね。
でもね…→
But, you see...
...how about now?
こうすれば　どうかしら？
She can do that, too?
こんなこともできるの！？
（２人）あっ！
Lower your sword, Hilda.
（イザベラ）剣を納めなさい　ヒルダ。
今のあなたは→
You are most definitely trespassing
into Lord En's territory.
明らかに　焔王坊っちゃまの
領界を侵犯しています。→
Any further and we will consider you
an enemy, and eliminate you by force.
これ以上は　敵意があるとみなし
強制的に排除しますよ？
敵意？勘違いするな　イザベラ→
Enemy? Don't misunderstand me, Isabella.
私は焔王坊っちゃまと
話をしに来ただけだ。
I simply came to speak with Lord En.
（サテュラ）
坊っちゃまは今　取り込み中だ。→
The Master is currently occupied!
話がしたけりゃ
アポとって出直してきな。
If you have something to say, schedule
an appointment and come back later!
Enemy? Don't make me laugh.
敵意だと？笑わせるな。→
You put my master in danger!
It's I who should be angry!
主君を危険にさらされて
頭にきてるのは私の方だ。
（２人）ああ…。
It was your retainer who first
drew arms against Beelze-sama!
先にベルゼ様に刃を向けたのに
貴様らの家臣だろう。→
And the person in the position
to stop it does nothing,
それを止められる立場の者が
止めようとせず→
all the while pretending to know
nothing and feigning innocence?!
知らぬ　存ぜぬと
とぼけることが→
敵意といわず…なんという！
Not my enemy?!
Incredulous!
ああっ！
♪♪～
焔王坊っちゃまを
甘やかすだけ甘やかし→
Lord En has been endlessly spoiled...
あんな　ふざけた態度を
取らせていること→
His frivolous attitude...
恥ずかしいと思わんのか！
...aren't you ashamed by it?!
Strong...
強ぇ…。
I didn't think she'd come this far...
《まさか　ここまでとは…
人間界に来て　何かが変わった→
What changed since she
came to the human world?
彼女を変える　それほどの
人間がいるというのか…》
Is there really a human out there
strong enough to change her?
Hilda-san!
ヒルダさ～～ん！あなた
やっぱり　サイコーっすよ～！
You're the best after
all! I never doubted you!
I believe I told you to
stand back, Creepichi.
下がっておれと
言っておろう…キモ市→
こんなもの
ただの前哨戦にすぎん。
This is nothing but the opening volley.
That's...
あれは…。
転送玉による空間の歪み…。
The warping of space from the transfer jewel!
きたか…。
So, they've come...
Okay, people. That's all
for your training for now.
（早乙女）よぉ～し　てめ～ら。→
ひとまず　修業は終わりだ。
よくやったな　くそったれ。
You did well, you piece of crap.
（早乙女）ご褒美にオレから
プレゼントだ！ジャン！
I'll give you this present as a reward.
Tada! It's the special Saotome School Gi!
早乙女流の道着！
どうだ　イカスだろ？
What do you think? Pretty awesome, right?
ちゃんと
赤ん坊の分もあるんだぜ！
I've got one for the baby, too!
イラね！
（男鹿）
ダッ！
No thanks.
（早乙女）おいっ！着ろよ！→
Hey! Put it on!
And respect your master!
そして　師匠と敬えよっ！
んなもんなくても感謝してらぁ。
大事なのはココだろ？
You don't have to do that
for us to thank you.
What's important is... in here, right?
何だ　ずいぶん　まともなことを
言うようになったじゃね～か→
What's this? That's being
pretty serious for a change.
Well, just get out there and give 'em hell.
まあ　せいぜい暴れてきな。
Yeah!
おう！
ダ～ッ！
With Yolda's power eliminated, have
they finally found this place?
ヨルダの能力が解除され
ようやく　ここを見つけたか…。
来るぞ　ここからが本番だ。
Here they come. This is when
the real battle begins.
Good going there, Demon Maidservants.
（ワスボガ）
ご苦労だったな　侍女悪魔…→
おまえ達は　もう用済みだ。
Your role has now ended.
This guy is... Behemoth?
こいつらが　ベヘモット…。
Are you Beelze-sama's contract holder?
お前が　ベルゼ様の契約者か？
ひぃっ！いやいや…。
ここには　いない。
No-no-no-no...
He's not here.
貴様らの相手は私がする。
I will be your opponent.
（ワスボガ）ベルゼ様の侍女悪魔か→
Beelze-sama's Demon Maidservant? I
thought you were done in by Hecadoth...
ヘカドスに殺られたんじゃ
なかったのか？
He had taken a human woman hostage.
この間は　人間の女を人質に
とられてな。それで→
That's what gave him the opening.
スキを作ってしまったが
今回は同じようにはいかんぞ。
I won't let the same thing happen again.
フッ…。
なめるな　侍女悪魔風情が！！
Don't belittle me, you
puny Demon Maidservant!
ハァ～…ハッ！
♪♪～
（ワスボガ）どわ～っ…！
たぁ～～！！
♪♪～
（ワスボガ）どわぁ～～…！→
I don't regret a single thing in my life!
我が生涯に一片の悔いなし～！！
襲撃か！？
An attack?
（古市）すげぇ…。
（ラミア）ヒルダ姉さま…。
Wow...
Miss Hilda!
あっ…。
Wait!
待て！
（姫川）おらぁ！そこまでだ！
Hey, that's far enough!
You're the bastards from
Akumano Academy, aren't you?
てめぇら
悪魔野学園のやつらだな！
Nice way to trash someone's
house, don't you think?
人ん家で　えらく派手に
やってくれたじゃねぇ～か。
人間が何のようだ！！
What the hell do you Humans want?!
Shut up, you!
（神崎）うるせぇぞ　こら～ッ！
（姫川）んん…。
W-Wait just a second!
（古市）
ちょ…ちょっと待って下さい。→
These people aren't from Akumano Academy...
この人たちは
悪魔野学園じゃなくて…。
（姫川・神崎）うわっ…。
（神崎・姫川）おっ…。
They're one of those "Ah, Kuma!" guys, right?
（東条）あっ！クマってやつか？
あっ…。
Let's finish this...
（東条）決着をつけようぜ…
この前のやつはどこだ？
Where's the bastard from before?
（寧々）大変なんです　姐さん。→
We're in trouble, Madam Aoi!
We're in Himekawa's apartment
building right now...
今　姫川のマンションに
いるんですけど→
悪魔野学園のやつらが
襲撃してきて…。
The bastards from Akumano
Academy have come to attack!
Akumano Academy?
（邦枝）悪魔の学園？
[TEL]（寧々）そ～です。今→
That's right...
Himekawa and Kanzaki are
facing them down now, but...
姫川と神崎たち
相手してるんですけど…。
（邦枝）あんた達　そいつらと
戦っちゃダメ！→
You guys can't go fighting with them!
Wait until I arrive!
私が行くまで待ってるのよ！
行くったって…どうすれば？
今からじゃ間に合わない…。
Go... But, how?
I won't make it at this rate.
（アンジェリカの鼻歌）
んっ！？
あなた　たしか…
（邦枝）
アランドロンの娘さん？
Wait, aren't you... Alaindelon's daughter?
Kunieda-san, was it?
（アンジェリカ）邦枝さん…でしたっけ？
You see, my father was
training at this temple...
実は父が　この
お寺で修業をしていたもので→
私も　そのお手伝いを。
And I have accompanied him.
アランドロンの
娘さんってことは→
Alaindelon's daughter...
同じ転送悪魔ってこと！？
あっ…。
That means you're also a Dimensional
Transfer Demon, right?
お願い　アンジェリカさん。
今すぐ　私を転送して！
Please, Angelica-san!
Transfer me this instant!
Damn you...
くそっ…。
（ナーガ）交代だ！→
It's my turn. You can't handle her.
この女　貴様では手にあまる。
やはり　貴様たちも来ていたか…。
So, you've come as well?
フッ　小娘が。
図に乗るなよ…。
Don't push your luck, girly.
（アランドロン）
三対一とは卑怯千万！
んっ！
Three versus one is not a fair battle!
（一同）んっ！？
Hilda-sama, I shall support you.
ヒルダ様
私めも　助太刀いたしますぞ。
修業とやらは　もういいのか？
You've finished with your training?
Yes, just as you can see.
ああ　見ての通り
バッチリよ。さぁて…→
I'm ready to go!
Now then... I'm going to beat
the living crap out of you!
てめぇら　ボッコボッコに殴るぞ！
ダァ～ブ～ッ！
Sorry to keep you all waiting.
I'll beat the crap outta you all!
Oga, what in the world special attack is...
Kunieda, you seem stronger somehow, too.
But this is a fight for me and Baby Beel.
Don't interfere!
On the next Beelzebub:
I Am The Parent!
Now then, Baby Beel... It's milktime!
Wait, Oga! That technique...
It's too dangerous!